# RAPHAEL BRET MOUNET

INTERN (707)-741-1326

#### • DETAILS •

(707)-741-1326 <a href="mailto:rbretmounet@gmail.com">rbretmounet@gmail.com</a>

• LINKS •

Github

Linkedin

**Website** 

• SKILLS •

SQL

HTML & CSS

Linux

PHP

Java

Matlab

Python

Git

C++

**Neural Networks** 

**Unreal Engine** 

Windows OS

Mac OS

LANGUAGES

English

French

# PROFILE

I am currently studying in college but my first few experiences in the professional space have been so positive that I can't wait to learn more in the real world and apply my skills. I am a quick learner and enjoy researching and learning new skills. I have a passion for tinkering with and building robots, looking at something complex only gets me excited to figure out how it works.

# **EMPLOYMENT HISTORY**

# Intern at Johnson Space Center, Houston, Texas Area

January 2019 — Present

Created a steady-state visually evoked potentials brain-computer interface which involved creating a Matlab program that could use live electroencephalogram(EEG) data and use a recurrent neural network to predict the frequency a user was looking at. Also, collected and analyzed EEG data, using a DSI-24 headset, for training and testing the neural networks.

## Cashier at Carl's Jr, Vallejo

September 2017 — June 2018

Worked at the drive-thru and front register taking orders, re-stocking ice in soda machines, sauces, cups, straws, napkins, replaced trash bags, brought trash to the dumpster, bagged and gave out orders, mopped/sweep floor, cleaned tables in the dining area, and cleaned bathrooms.

#### EDUCATION

#### B.S. Computer Engineer, Diablo Valley College, Pleasant Hill

August 2018 — March 2022

Currently attending a community college in pursuit of transferring to UC San Diego for a B.S. in Computer Engineering.

# High School Diploma, Benicia High School, Benicia

August 2016 — May 2018

## COURSES

Introduction to Programming C++, Diablo Valley College January 2018 — May 2018

Adv Programming with C & C++, Diablo Valley College

August 2018 — December 2018

Assembly Prog/Comp Org, Diablo Valley College

January 2020 — May 2020

Prog Design & Data Structures C++, Diablo Valley College

August 2020 — December 2020

Python Data Structures, University of Michigan

November 2020 - November 2020

Using Python to Access Web Data, University of Michigan

December 2020 — December 2020

Using Databases with Python, University Of Michigan

December 2020 — December 2020

#### ■ REFERENCES

References available upon request